Friends, through this video we are going to know in detail about the
quarter 4 result of ICICI PDA Life Insurance Company.  The
company has
published its audited financial result
of the standalone and consolidated company along with it final dividend of ₹1.65
per equity share which is a good
thing.  Let us know about its result.
I am going to share the consolidated financial results with you.
Consolidated result means the result published by the
parent company along with the associated company is
called consolidated result and the
result published with the figures in this report is
according to these lax.  The
income that we are getting to see in this quarter is Rs.
crore 555 lakh which was Rs.
crore 4 lakh in the previous quarter and Rs. 15637
crore 51 lakh in the previous year, so as per the previous quarter,
we are getting to see a big decline in the income
and as per the previous year
also, we are getting to see a big decline in the income.
Let us now
know about its expenses.   The
expenses that we are seeing are Rs
crore 81 lakh which
was Rs 200353 crore 64 lakh in the previous quarter and Rs
2477 crore 70 lakh in the previous year.
Expenses are also
seen increasing as per the previous quarter and as per the previous year.
If the expenses are high,
its direct impact
is seen on the company's profit.
Let us check
how much net profit the company has generated in this quarter.   The
net profit seen in this quarter is Rs
623 crore 91 lakh,
which was Rs 387 crore 15 lakh in the previous quarter
and Rs 385 crore 28 lakh in the previous year.  If we
look at the previous quarter, we can
see an increase in profit
and as per the previous year also we can
see an increase in profit.
Which is a good thing.  Its direct
impact will definitely be seen on the stock value of the company.
Friends, if you are
watching the video for the first time,
please support the channel by subscribing to it.
Let us now know about the EPS value of this stock.  The
EPS value which was 2.66 has
now increased to 4.28.  Please do let us know in the comment section
how much quantity you hold in this stock.